[water splashes]
[Killua] Wait. "ika" means squid,
And you're an octopus, aren't you?
[Ikalgo sputters]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[singer singing in English]
[narrator] Assassins attack
as Gon and Killua split up
to stop the selection process.
One of them is Ikalgo,
an octopus-type chimera ant.
[yells]
Long time, no see, huh?
[chuckles]
Don't tell me you can't swim.
Uh, oh, uh, well--
If you went in there
with those wounds,
they'd tear you to shreds
in no time at all. Am I wrong?
Uh, well, I don't think
I would have put it that way exactly,
but I suppose, uh--
-[Flutter] Ikalgo!
-[gasps]
Did you finish off the kid?
Not quite yet. We're still fighting.
Eh? Wait. Who are you talking to?
[shrieks] I screwed up!
Oh, that's right.
You guys can communicate
telepathically.
Your boss, he's the guy
who was flying over me, wasn't he?
Now hold on.
I can see why you might think--
-[Flutter] Hey! Ikalgo!
-That's what I was doing--
I'm not going to send
my satellite dragonflies,
because if the enemy sees them
flying about inside the cave,
they will get suspicious.
Okay, so let's make a deal.
I'll give you ten seconds.
[gasps]
[Ikalgo whimpers]
Six seconds.
and my favorite was the breathtaking
whiplash squid.
Octopi are ugly.
[Killua thinking]
Yeah. I saw it in your eyes.
[Ikalgo] I only hope
that in my next life,
I will be reborn as a squid.
[Killua gasps]
[Shark Ant growls]
-[gasps]
-[Killua gasps]
-Huh?
-[Shark Ant laughs]
You lowered your guard!
I bet you didn't think fish
could jump, huh?
I'll crush you
and the rock behind you!
[gasps]
[Flutter] Ikalgo, come in.
[Ikalgo] Uh, yes.
Th… The fight's not over yet.
[Flutter] What's happening?
Has he used weapons, or special abilities?
-[Ikalgo grunting]
-Ikalgo!
[Ikalgo] No.
In fact,
he's been fighting with his bare hands.
[Shark Ant] Aw, come on!
Scream a little.
Otherwise, it's no fun, huh?
Or are you in too much pain to talk, huh?
You're right. He was scum!
That's why he was the decoy!
I did it, Sir Ortho!
I've attached the badge!
Damn. The bleeding still won't stop.
[Killua] Wait. Was that a digital sound
inside my head?
[gasps]
What?
A fish?
But I'm not in the water!
What in the hell is going on here?
I didn't sense anything at all.
[gasps]
This is bad.
I don't have the slightest idea
where these attacks are coming from.
[Sir Ortho laughs]
A hundred and eight points!
Well, you'll figure it out
if you can survive
long enough, anyway.
[gasps]
These fish are made from Nen.
I should be able to sense them,
so why can't I?
Something is triggering them
from somewhere else.
That has to be it!
How else could I be attacked
by something I can't see, or even sense?
[grunting]
Now, then, have you determined
anything about these attacks?
[Killua] It looks like
he can only materialize
three fish at any one time.
After that, the fish will disappear,
That is correct,
but unfortunately for you,
figuring it out
isn't gonna help you much.
so blocking them is impossible.
[laughs]
By the way, your left shoulder
is worth 54 points.
I have a special dartboard, you see.
Like for example…
[Killua grunts]
[Sir Ortho]
Your right elbow is 27 points.
Your right hand is 18 points.
[laughs] Ninety-nine points.
Hey, what's wrong?
I can't hear your screams.
Triple six!
Four!
Thirteen!
[Lady Ortho clapping]
Way to go, brother.
That was incredible.
You're on a roll now.
[Sir Ortho] Well, naturally.
Our lives are on the line.
[narrator] This is how the Ortho
siblings' power works.
The younger sister creates a Nen pin,
There is no way
to avoid this attack.
That is because,
until they've hit the target's body,
the Nen needlefish do not exist,
[narrator] Of course,
the siblings do incur some risk.
Once the pin activates,
they are invincible.
But if the brother misses
on the final throw and busts…
[Killua grunts]
[narrator] …all the damage
the target has taken
will transfer back to the siblings.
and beg for his life,
it would certainly help me focus,
and I could be far more effective.
But if he were to say something
like, "Please hurry up, and kill me,"
or if he played the nihilist hero
and said,
I would rather he die
while dreading the exact moment
when the final shot will come.
[grunts]
[gasps]
I've lost way too much blood already.
[Sir Ortho] Right calf!
Leave it to me.
You see?
Bravo! [laughs]
-Yay!
[both] Yay!
Mwah! You're the best big brother
in the whole wide world!
-I'm going to go check his corpse!
-I'll come with you.
We should share some of the meat
with Coburn as a reward.
[Gon gobbling]
You're not eating?
Whoa!
[Gon] Isn't that enough?
Hell, no! Are you kidding me?
So you were lying to me?
[sputters]
I'm not like those other guys!
He's strong, but he's just a kid.
I'm putting my life in the hands
of a little boy who doesn't have a clue.
And besides, if you're lying,
it'll be a lot easier for me.
I could just kill you, you know.
[dramatic music playing]
[Meleoron]
This kid, the look in his eyes,
There's something special
about this kid.
I can't even tell how much power
he really has.
[Sir Ortho laughs]
You hit him right in the forehead.
What a shot.
[Sir Ortho] Sir Flutter,
we've taken out the target.
[Flutter] Really? Excellent.
I'll be sure to inform Sir Leol
that a promotion is in order.
An octopus's suction cup.
[gasps] No way.
But how in the world
did you manage to do that?
No, what I mean is my…
my darts are perfect!
They're completely
impossible to block!
Yeah, except I didn't block it.
I just grabbed it, that's all.
I waited 'til the last moment,
right when it materialized at my head.
[gasps]
I had plenty of time
to break the fish's beak,
take a sucker,
and put it right at the end of it.
are fast enough to catch a dart.
Not you, not anyone!
Do you hear me, brat?
[Killua] Yeah, you're right.
If I hadn't known
where the dart was gonna be,
I wouldn't have been able to.
But fortunately for me,
I knew just where it would hit,
and I was dead right.
Don't you remember?
The first throw you had
was a double four.
a sign you were confident
in your skill.
Players like that will always play
by the official rules.
If they're confident and trained,
process it, and transmit
a command to his hand,
he programmed the aura
around his hand
to send a signal
directly to his muscles,
This is what happens
when you get cocky…
[Killua thinking] Or was I seven?
-…are so stupid!
-[Killua] Doesn't really matter.
-Shouldn't have talked so long.
-[Orthos arguing]
Gotta hurry up.
Huh?
I can't get my body to move.
Is this really happening?
It almost feels like
I'm taking a warm bath.
Damn it. Now I feel cold.
That's just great.
Am I going to die here?
Gon, I'm sorry.
[Killua] What are you doing?
Hey, isn't it obvious?
I'm turning traitor, you dummy!
Not cool, I know. Now stop talking!
Look, I know an unlicensed doctor.
We can take
the underground current.
Won't be long, so hang on!
[Killua] Are you an idiot? Come on.
I spared your life.
Now they're gonna
come after you, too.
Yeah, don't you think I know that?
Don't ask me why I'm doing this.
All I know is this.
I can't stand by while you die!
I'm gonna save you!
[echoing] Don't you die on me!
[closing theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[Gon] Next time,
"power and games."
[Meleoron exhales]
[Gon] If you smoke,
your teeth will turn black.
[Meleoron] I'm a chameleon,
so I don't have teeth.
[singer singing in Japanese]